SPC Matthew Levandowski

1041 College Ave NE Grand Rapids, MI 49503 315.286.2383 (mobile) levandowski.matthew@gmail.com http://www2.gvsu.edu/~levandma/

Objective

Experienced military leader with documented success in responsible and challenging positions; seeking a position to gain work related experience in order to progress to higher level positions. I have a proven record of accomplishment, mission-critical decision making, time-management, and extensive teamwork abilities; with the ability to develop and implement effective action plans. I have fulfilled a tour of duty in Afghanistan and four years of military service with an honorable discharge.

Education

Grand Valley State University

Allendale, MI

B.A.Sc., Computer Science (Grades: 80%)

Sep. 2009 - Jun. 2011

- Minor: Business
- Relevant courses: Java programming, Data Structures and Algorithms, Digital Design, Computer Architecture, C programming, System Programming, SQL

Muskegon Community College

Muskegon, MI

2001-2006

- A.S.A., Science and Arts
 - Finished degree after completing 4 year Active Duty contract with the U.S. Army.
 - Relevant courses: Physics, Calculus, Statistics, Electroacoustic music

Work Experience

Kohls Department Store

Grandville, MI

Advertisement Setter / Warehouse

Nov 2009 - Jun 2011

- Work with other associates as a team to inventory and assess advertisement pricing and policies for entire store.
- Customer assistance and interaction
- Warehouse inventory and offsite merchandise management

180th Transportation Co., U.S. Army Reserve

Muskegon, MI

25F Communication Specialist

Aug 2009 - Aug. 2010

Train on various soldier skills and wheeled truck driving. Plan and execute regular training exercises
in support of the 180th Transportation Company.

Shareco Communications

Grand Rapids, MI

Telecommunications Line Installer

Mar. 2008 - Nov. 2008

- I was responsible for the installation, repair, and termination of cabling in commercial and residential business.
- Proficient in the use of CAT5E, CAT6, 100-pair copper wire, and standard RG5 coaxial cable.
- Installation and splicing of fiber optic lines in commercial settings.

710 BSB, 3rd BCT, 10th MTN DIV, U.S. Army

Afghanistan

Communications Specialist OEF VII

Feb. 2006 - Jul. 2007

- Deployed in support of Operation Enduring Freedom as a communication specialist for a company sized element with more than 150 employees.
- Participated in the Joint Task Force as security for the occupying NATO and ISAF forces.
- Participated in the successful repatriation of a US Soldier in a Search and Rescue Mission.
- Maintained and Installed radio communication and navigation devices in armored vehicles.

10th Mountain Division, U.S. Army

Fort Drum, NY

25F Network Switching Systems Operator / Maintainer

Aug. 2005 - Feb. 2006

- Directly responsible for the installation, maintenance, and repair of over half a million dollars of communication equipment for a company with over 150 soldiers.
- Participated in successful training at JROTC in Fort Polk, Louisiana.
- Conducted numerous training exercises successfully in light infantry.

Military Awards		
Joint Service Achievement Medal (Secretary of Defense)	May 2007	
ISAF Medal Afghanistan (NATO)	2007	
Joint Meritorious Unit Award (CJTF-76)	2007	
Army Commendation Medal (U.S. Army)	2007	
Army Good Conduct Medal (x2) (U.S. Army)	2007	
Army Certification of Achievement (U.S. Army)	2006	
Security Clearance		
Secret (US Army)	Exp. 2012	
Skills		

Programming: Java, C/C++, Ruby, Python, BASH, HTML, CSS, SQL

Operating Systems: Linux (Debian, Gentoo, ArchLinux), Mac OSX, Solaris, UNIX, Windows 95/98/NT/2000/XP/VISTA/WIN 7

Applications: Vim, Eclipse, LATEX, MS Office 2007, Adobe Photoshop/Premiere

Military Skills: General Dynamics C4 - MSE Network Systems, COMTECH MTS, Plugr, and BlueForce Tracker GPS devices, COMSEC devices, SIPR and NIPR networks, SINCGARS Radios, SMART-T Satellite Communications, Cisco routers

Miscellaneous: software configuration management, strong verbal and written communication skills, excellent troubleshooting skills, exceptional problem solving skills, good team skills.

Interests

Academic: Ubiquitous Computing, RF/wireless, Operating Systems design / maintenance, Computer Security, Information Assurance

Memberships: Student Veteran Organization, CS Study Group, Total Trek Quest

Copyright 2011 Matthew Levandowski: This resume was written entirely in Latex and licensed under the Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 3.0 Unported License.